<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219060500 +0000" stop="20250219063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Total Loss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman has problems keeping her husband's company solvent after his death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219063500 +0000" stop="20250219070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Dark Step</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man tries to get away from one woman so he can marry another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219070500 +0000" stop="20250219080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Desert Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mannix travels to New Mexico to prove that a Native American's death was murder, he runs into resistance from the townsfolk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219080500 +0000" stop="20250219090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of The Damned</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When a counterfeiting suspect escapes custody, rumors fly that Jim Farragut, the cop in charge of him, succumbed to either greed or cowardice. Jim's an old friend, so Cannon agrees to find a witness Jim claims can prove that he neither took a bribe nor experienced a failure of courage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219090500 +0000" stop="20250219100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sing A Song Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The managers of a rock music star, whom they think drowned in his pool, cash in on his "tragedy""."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219100000 +0000" stop="20250219103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese widow is senselessly murdered, leaving her small daughter an orphan. Friday has a hard time controlling his emotions while seeking the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219103000 +0000" stop="20250219110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang of juvenile thieves have been stealing petty items in order to gain membership into an exclusive club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219110000 +0000" stop="20250219113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 76 -- The Militants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed participate in the search for two black militants who ambush and critically wound two officers in their patrol car. When one of the suspects subsequently dies in custody, a bitter public relations battle begins with the militant group as the search for the other suspect continues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219113000 +0000" stop="20250219120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 164 -- The Poachers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young employee at the city garage steals a patrol car and engages in a high speed pursuit. Afterward, Malloy and Reed arrest a young woman trying to cash an old-age benefits check she found on the ground, report to an apartment complex garage that had its security camera stolen, investigate a break-in at a mortuary and arrest a couple of pill pushers at a warehouse in Officer Ed Well's territory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219120000 +0000" stop="20250219130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill's Book Of Fables</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill writes a book to teach Toony a lesson about morals."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219130000 +0000" stop="20250219133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Grass Is Always Greener</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally make friends with the garbage man's kids, Chris and Pete. They quickly learn that they take for granted what they have. Simple things like just having a yard to play in leave Chris and Pete in awe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219133000 +0000" stop="20250219140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Boat Builders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally, Chester and Tooey are building their own boat and plan to sail on it, despite Ward and June's forbidding Wally. Once at the lake, Beaver is the only one small enough to get in it and once on the water, the boat tips over leaving a soaked Beaver behind. However, it's trying to keep their afternoon of boating a secret from Ward and June, that's really going to wipe Wally and Beaver out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219140000 +0000" stop="20250219150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Playboy Pugilist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Boxing trainer Jimmy West thinks he's finally found a championship contender in Davey Carroll. Unfortunately, Davey's tangled love life leads to Jimmy being charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219150000 +0000" stop="20250219160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lovelorn  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend a man who has been accused of murdering the relationship columnist whose response ended his relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219160000 +0000" stop="20250219170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Gunshot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil is forced to shoot a suspect in an armed robbery. He has trouble dealing with the consequences of his actions, after he realizes the person he shot was a teenaged girl - and no one can locate the gun he believed she was pointing at him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219170000 +0000" stop="20250219180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy goes on his first turkey hunt with his father and two of his friends</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219180000 +0000" stop="20250219190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Island In The Desert: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus, in the desert hunting escaped killer Gard Dixon, is wounded by the outlaw. He is found by Ben Snow, a half-crazy hermit who has been living in the desert with his gold for many years.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219190000 +0000" stop="20250219200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Meredith Smith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Jake Smith dies and leaves his estate to Meredith Smith. Then several claimants to the estate show up saying they are Meredith. It's up to Ben, the executor of the estate, to determine the true heir.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219200000 +0000" stop="20250219203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Town Slept</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The town of North Fork becomes a haven for outlaws when suave Ben Judson smooth-talks his way into the marshal's job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219203000 +0000" stop="20250219210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Milly's Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A veteran returns with tales of heroism and the fate of Milly's brother in the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219210000 +0000" stop="20250219220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tom O'neal Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E31</episode-num>
    <desc>"Tom O'Neal and Ellen Howard want to get married, but their parents object, so Tom takes money from his father's savings and runs away with Ellen. They soon realize that that was an unwise decision."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219220000 +0000" stop="20250219230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Tycoons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>John gets everyone but Roy excited about buying into a nearby hot dog stand. By the time Roy gets interested, the stand burns down. A man is injured in an accident with a power lawn mower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219230000 +0000" stop="20250219233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yankee Doodle Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is designated as the setting for the making of an army film on Mobile Army Surgical Hospital units. Hawkeye is chosen as the star while Margaret and Frank compose a screenplay. Hawkeye objects to the piece of propaganda that filmmaker Lt. Bricker is producing and, having exposed the original film, reshoots a new one his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250219233000 +0000" stop="20250220000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bananas, Crackers And Nuts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Henry goes for some R&amp;R, Hawkeye pretends to crack up so that Frank will let him and Trapper go on some R&amp;R.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220000000 +0000" stop="20250220003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>John Hodges, a chopper pilot referred to as The Cowboy, has been hit in the shoulder, and arrives at the 4077th. He is expecting a letter—he's worried that his wife, Jean, is leaving him for another man. He wants to go home, but Henry refuses, stating Cowboy's wound isn't serious enough to merit a stateside ticket. Bad luck then follows Henry Blake like the seat of his pants!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220003000 +0000" stop="20250220010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry, Please Come Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Col. Henry Blake is transferred to Tokyo and Frank starts imposing military discipline on the camp, the surgeons will do anything to get Henry back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220010000 +0000" stop="20250220013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>One-punch Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie must learn to defend himself against a bully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220013000 +0000" stop="20250220020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Governor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is goaded into ticketing the governor's car and mistakenly believes Andy is setting him up for a dressing-down by the governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220020000 +0000" stop="20250220023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Monster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro has an idea of starting a new business, a five-second car wash. But Jed and Granny don’t care for the idea and think that Jethro and Elly need jobs to fill their time. At the bank, Milburn is taking care of his nephew, little Milby. Jane doesn’t want to take care of the sneaky child and Drysdale doesn’t have the time. When Jed visits asking for jobs for Elly and Jethro, he says that Elly May can take care of Milby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220023000 +0000" stop="20250220030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Captures A Submarine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The men are on a simple reconnaissance mission, but Gomer somehow seems destined to ruin it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220030000 +0000" stop="20250220033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Tower</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan blackmails General Burkhalter to keep Klink from being transferred to the Russian front for failing to keep Hogan from blowing up a radio tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220033000 +0000" stop="20250220040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Colonel Klink's Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink suffers at the hands of a tough sergeant sent to discipline prisoners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220040000 +0000" stop="20250220043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Betty White</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Bug, Carol thinks there's a bug in her hotel bed. Then, in The Family, Eunice celebrates Mama's birthday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220043000 +0000" stop="20250220053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Petulant Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret was a much younger woman on the make who entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220053500 +0000" stop="20250220060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Ninety Years Without Slumbering</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man fears that he will die if his grandfather clock stops running.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220060500 +0000" stop="20250220063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Morning Of The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A young woman is apprehensive about meeting her future mother-in-law for the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220063500 +0000" stop="20250220070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Diamond Necklace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is told he has to retire from his job at the jewelry store where he has worked most of his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220070500 +0000" stop="20250220080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Survivor Who Wasn't</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man survives a plane crash—or does he? His wife has her doubts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220080500 +0000" stop="20250220090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Well Remembered Terror</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mobsters kidnap Judge Hayes's daughter, on the orders of their boss who is on trial in Hayes's courtroom. Cannon must find and rescue her before the judge is forced to preside over a miscarriage of justice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220090500 +0000" stop="20250220100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Testament Of Power</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The executors of a millionaire's estate attempt to get rid of a new will putting them out of their jobs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220100000 +0000" stop="20250220103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man has been found in a locked room, along with a gun that could not have been the murder weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220103000 +0000" stop="20250220110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Grenade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A surly teenager throws acid on the back of another student and later crashes a party armed with a live hand grenade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220110000 +0000" stop="20250220113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 16 -- Child In Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a tavern robbery in progress, and then are jolted by a severe domestic abuse situation they are powerless to stop. In the meantime, they lose track of a naive college girl who has just been carjacked by a convicted rapist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220113000 +0000" stop="20250220120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 56 -- Vice Versa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Malloy has allowed his driver's license to expire, Reed has to do the driving on today's busy patrol. They search for an ice cream truck driver who's been trying to sell marijuana to children, get an unexpected reaction from a bank robber, help a man who's had his house completely emptied by his neighbors, deal with a woman who shoots her husband dead and find a live baby in a trashcan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220120000 +0000" stop="20250220130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>*cabin Fever</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony cope with "cabin fever!""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220130000 +0000" stop="20250220133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Plays Hooky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver find themselves tardy for the third time this week and decide to skip altogether. However, they quickly find themselves caught when they accidentally walk on the set of a live TV show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220133000 +0000" stop="20250220140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Garage Painters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lazy weekend leads Ward to direct Wally and Beaver to read a book, Tom Sawyer. The book influences them so much that they take on the job of painting the garage doors. However, they soon find the job to be awfully boring and messy. Chaos erupts when neighbor Bengie Bellamy stops by wanting to help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220140000 +0000" stop="20250220150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Double-entry Mind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Timid bookkeeper Clem Sandover is irate when his longterm embezzlement scheme is discovered by a fellow employee. When that co-worker turns up dead, however, it's Sandover's wife who's charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220150000 +0000" stop="20250220160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Genius  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's nephew, Irwin, is charged with murder, his investigation leads to a high-tech computer firm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220160000 +0000" stop="20250220170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Country Mouse, City Mouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil's visiting niece and Bubba's nephew team up in an effort to escape the boredom of small town life. But they get more excitement than they bargained for when they cross paths with a dangerous parolee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220170000 +0000" stop="20250220180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Typewriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy borrows an antique typewriter from the Baldwin sisters so he can submit a proper manuscript to a magazine</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220180000 +0000" stop="20250220190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Island In The Desert: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While Matt and Newly hunt for Festus, Ben Snow and Festus attempt to haul his gold out of the desert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220190000 +0000" stop="20250220200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Mighty Is The Word</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunfighter gets religion and becomes a preacher only to be confronted by a vengeful man whose brother he once killed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220200000 +0000" stop="20250220203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A head wound wipes out Lucas' memory, leaving him with only one clue: he's wearing an outlaw's gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220203000 +0000" stop="20250220210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Executioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A former neighbor of the McCain's is released from jail after serving his sentence for stage coach robbery, but the money was never found. Lucas agrees to let the man work for him, but the new work hand holds a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220210000 +0000" stop="20250220220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarence Mullins Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke and Charlie leave the train for supplies and to see Duke's old friends at a fort. One is a minister who was cashiered out of the Army who is trying to create peace with the Modocs despite a Major who only wants to kill all Indians."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220220000 +0000" stop="20250220230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Nuisance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>John becomes the victim of a hit and run. While hospitalized, he flirts with his physical therapist and deals with a nurse who seems to have it in for him. The rest of the station must adjust to a difficult replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220230000 +0000" stop="20250220233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate A Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of thefts breaks out in the camp. Missing pieces include Frank's silver picture frame, Margaret's hair brush and Trapper's watch. The camp is searched and everything is found in Hawkeye's locker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250220233000 +0000" stop="20250221000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Germ Warfare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye moves a wounded North Korean soldier into The Swamp, rather than let him be shipped out before he's stable. During the night he and Trapper play Dracula, and siphon off a pint of Frank's blood. The soldier then contracts hepatitis, so they have to test Frank without him knowing, and have to keep him away from Margaret and the patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221000000 +0000" stop="20250221003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes home, describing Christmas in Korea: Radar ships a jeep home, a piece at a time; Henry gives the monthly lecture on sex, with the aid of figure A and figure B; Trapper helps deliver a calf; Klinger and Frank get into a fight, but Father Mulcahy smoothes things over; Hawkeye and Trapper sabotage Margaret's tent; Hawkeye flies to the front line dressed as Santa to help a wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221003000 +0000" stop="20250221010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Edwina</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses go to extreme lengths to find a date for Nurse Eddie—they won't go out with anyone until Eddie gets a date. The men draw straws, and Hawkeye is the big loser, especially after Eddie nearly kills him in a scene resembling teenage "mating" rituals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221010000 +0000" stop="20250221013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Hurry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Big businessman Malcolm Tucker is stuck in Mayberry on a Sunday when his car breaks down outside the city limits. He's soon driven to frustration when he finds there is no way to get anything done until the following day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221013000 +0000" stop="20250221020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>High Noon In Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets hysterical when Andy receives a letter from a man he arrested and sent to prison. The convict is to be released soon and says in the letter that he is coming to settle the score with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221020000 +0000" stop="20250221023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Duke Becomes A Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampett's dog, Duke, seems sad. Probably because, they figure, he misses Claudette, the poodle Mrs. Drysdale’s dog, Claude, is now with. Jethro then brings Jed a letter from Paris, France, which the clan figures is from Mlle. Denise, who brought Claudette over. Jed looks at the letter, seeing it is in French, and heads down to the bank, where Mrs. Drysdale is anticipating Claude and Claudette’s puppies, for Jane to read it. In the letter, Mlle. Denise says she is coming to Beverly Hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221023000 +0000" stop="20250221030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Grudge Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter, perhaps overestimating his skill set, challenges the fleet's retired boxing champion to a fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221030000 +0000" stop="20250221033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Top Secret Top Coat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a top-secret document from Klink's coat to save him from being arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221033000 +0000" stop="20250221040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to let him play camp commander so he can get a French agent released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221040000 +0000" stop="20250221043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Eydie Gorme</sub-title>
    <desc>In Stella Toddler, Carol plays an accident-prone woman whose recover is inhibited by her hospital roommate. Then, in The Man Without a Green Thumb, Tim fights with an aggressive plant. Finally, in The Oldest Man, Vicki is tortured by the Oldest Man, who's so old he only hurts himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221043000 +0000" stop="20250221053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dangerous Dowager</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Matilda Benson is a tough old broad who rules her children with an iron hand and the promises in her will. When Benson and her brood become involved in a gambling scandal and the death of a nightclub owner, Mason looks into the matriarch's matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221053500 +0000" stop="20250221060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Ring-a-ding Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A movie star receives a ring from her home town fan club. In it she sees the faces of people she knows telling her she's needed there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221060500 +0000" stop="20250221063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Relative Value</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man schemes to become the sole heir to his rich uncle's estate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221063500 +0000" stop="20250221070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Right Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A burglar bargains with his victim when he discovers robbery will not be very profitable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221070500 +0000" stop="20250221080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Choice Of Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix looks into a businessman's murder, discovering that the man's wife may have been the real target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221080500 +0000" stop="20250221090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Arena Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Socialite Doris Hawthorne's fiance disappears. Only then does she learn he was actually married to a Swiss woman, and also a blackmailing extortionist with a long list of enemies, many of whom want his files.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221090500 +0000" stop="20250221100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Go Round</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>It's one killing after another as Barnaby investigates a hit-and-run accident while wealthy townspeople plot his murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221100000 +0000" stop="20250221103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221103000 +0000" stop="20250221110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221110000 +0000" stop="20250221113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 106 -- Post Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After beginning the search for a well known suspect who just stole a 600-pound offset printing press, Reed and Malloy try to convince an 85-year-old man to leave the soon-to-be demolished apartment building where he's resided alone for 27 years. Afterward, they pull over a very unusual vehicle, and chase a delivery truck to the end of an unfinished bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221113000 +0000" stop="20250221120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 88 -- Reason To Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a riding stable run by retired actor Slim Berkeley. The owner is careless about trusting people and has $100 and a gold belt buckle stolen. Because of a criminal record in New York his young assistant runs, but when searched nothing is found. A call to a phone booth where the man inside is being attacked leads to a drug arrest and sore jaw for Reed. Reed spots a robbery at a drive-in resulting in a shoot-out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221120000 +0000" stop="20250221130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toony And Bill Dial-up 1995</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill takes Toony on a virtual reality tour of 1995 pop culture."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221130000 +0000" stop="20250221133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Pug Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When the new girl, Gloria, tells Wally that he has a pug nose, he becomes incredibly self-conscious and purchases a contraption that is suppose to give him a strong Roman nose. When Ward discovers the device, he gives him a pep talk which just makes matters worse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221133000 +0000" stop="20250221140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Pigeons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Larry and Whitey begin a pigeon club and they each purchase pigeons of their own. Beaver names his two Miss Canfield and Miss Landers, after his two teachers. However, when Beaver comes down with chicken pox, Wally is forced into caring for them, but soon finds Beaver isn't the only one ill, Miss Canfield and Miss Landers are also ailing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221140000 +0000" stop="20250221150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hateful Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Young cop Jimmy Anderson and his veteran partner come across a robbery at the Wilson Plastics Company while on patrol one night. His partner killed in the ensuing shootout, evidence then points to Jimmy as having been an accomplice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221150000 +0000" stop="20250221160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It appears that a ghost has hired Matlock when the attorney learns the man who hired him to defend his wife is in fact the man she is accused of murdering!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221160000 +0000" stop="20250221170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie suspects that JoAnn's new cook is connected to the murder of a young prostitute. But Virgil suspects the culprit maybe a local pimp who has been intimidating the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221170000 +0000" stop="20250221180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A meteorite crashes through the roof of the Baldwin sisters' "Recipe"" room</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221180000 +0000" stop="20250221190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lee J. Cobb and his daughter, Julie, appear together for the first time when Cobb guest stars as a once-proud military officer who is suddenly faced with a painful and unplanned reunion with his daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221190000 +0000" stop="20250221200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Strange One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ponderosa becomes a site of refuge for a woman suspected of being a witch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221200000 +0000" stop="20250221203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Marshal Torrance is heading home from a cattle sale with Lucas and Mark when the old lawman mysteriously disappears. They trace him to a nearby Mexican ghost town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221203000 +0000" stop="20250221210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alphonso's wife gives birth, the bandits holding Marshal Torrance relax their guard, enabling Lucas and Mark to rescue the old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221210000 +0000" stop="20250221220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The David Garner Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>"Hale is entrusted to deliver $8,000 to a bank. Young David Garner is determined to steal it and he stows along on the wagon train, along with a girl who's in love with him. Following them is a shady man who seems to have a hold over David."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221220000 +0000" stop="20250221230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John are assigned to work the big football game at the Coliseum. A woman accidentally pulls her husband off the roof into a tree. At the game, the paramedics treat a choking victim, a man with breathing difficulties, an injured photographer and a TV announcer with heart trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221230000 +0000" stop="20250221233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a Dear John recording from home. Hawkeye and Trapper try to set him up with a date, but fail. Radar is taken by a new nurse at the camp and she is into poetry and music, so they coach him. Margaret wants to stop the relationship, so Hawkeye and Trapper get between her and Frank until she relents. Radar's "Ahhhh, Bach!" and "That's highly significant" quotes win him the girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250221233000 +0000" stop="20250222000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tuttle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye creates a fake doctor, Captain Jonathan S. Tuttle, to give supplies to the local orphans. Henry wants Tuttle to be officer of the day, so Hawkeye creates a fake personnel file, and all his back pay is given to the orphanage. When General Clayton wants to reward his generosity, Hawkeye is forced to invent a story about Tuttle jumping from a chopper without his parachute!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222000000 +0000" stop="20250222003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Ringbanger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper operate on a famous Colonel - after discovering that he is particularly ruthless about sacrificing his men, they come up with a scheme to get him sent back to the states with a little unwitting help from Frank, Margaret, and a drunk Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222003000 +0000" stop="20250222010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sometimes You Hear The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank throws his back out while spending the evening with Margaret, and ends up in traction. He promptly applies for the Purple Heart, having been 'technically' wounded at a frontline unit. Tommy Gillis, an old friend of Hawkeye's, is writing a book about the war, and pays him a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222010000 +0000" stop="20250222013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Loaded Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped goat eats a case of dynamite that was going to be used for blasting and puts Mayberry in danger—especially when Otis Campbell gets drunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222013000 +0000" stop="20250222020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Class Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy meets up with his high school sweetheart at their reunion and it appears they could be rekindling their relationship. But do they want the same things, and did they ever?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222020000 +0000" stop="20250222023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Inherits A Castle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro tells Jed that he has inherited a castle in England, after hearing the word from Drysdale. He gets costumes from Tudor times, thinking that Queen Elizabeth I is still reigning. Jethro even makes Granny wear an oaf costume, since she doesn’t have Clampett blood. Drysdale and Jane visit, and Jane tells the Clampetts that what Jethro is telling them is wrong. But after Drysdale paints a picture for Jane, the two convince the Clampetts to go, even providing an oaf for Jethro, Miss Jane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222023000 +0000" stop="20250222030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer, Star Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer witnesses a car accident involving Sgt. Carter, who is at fault. Rather than have Gomer testify against him, the sergeant schemes for Gomer to be out of town on the court date.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222030000 +0000" stop="20250222033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Crittendon Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon disrupts Hogan's plan to blow up a tunnel and stop a convoy of rocket fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222033000 +0000" stop="20250222040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Some Of Their Planes Are Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Germans plan to send their men into England via captured planes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222040000 +0000" stop="20250222043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In Stella Toddler and the Oldest Man, Carol plays an accident-prone woman who buys shoes from the Oldest Man. Then, in Flora, the gang parodies classic film-noir "Laura", with Carol as Gene Tierney and Steve as Dana Andrews.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222043000 +0000" stop="20250222053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Toy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Selkirk is a major league rotter who wants Claire Allison in the worst way, even though she's dating Dirk Benedict. Selkirk has Dirk's jaw broken and begins sending Claire threatening mail. Then Selkirk is murdered in his beach house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222053500 +0000" stop="20250222060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>You Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Driving home one rainy evening, a man accidentally hits a boy on a bicycle. Determined to hide his guilt, the man flees the scene—but his car has other ideas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222060500 +0000" stop="20250222063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Take Care Of You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A used car salesman is driven to murder by his big-spending wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222063500 +0000" stop="20250222070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Avon Emeralds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A Scotland Yard detective is assigned to tail a woman and prevent her from smuggling jewels out of England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222070500 +0000" stop="20250222080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Word Called Courage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Haunted by the fact that he broke under torture during the Korean War, one of Mannix's former comrades kidnaps the detective, subjecting him to the same torture he underwent to prove that anybody would crack under such treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222080500 +0000" stop="20250222090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Photo Finish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank agrees to look into a murder, convinced the Indian suspect did not commit the crime. His investigation unearths dozens of missing Indians and a drug smuggling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222090500 +0000" stop="20250222100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>To Denise, With Love And Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A philanderer murders his mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222100000 +0000" stop="20250222103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Doctor In The Roundhouse?: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After Floyd Smoot is jilted by his mail-ordered sweetheart, Kate tries to restore his self-confidence by pretending to be in love with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222103000 +0000" stop="20250222110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship Of Floyd Smoot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe gets into the cologne business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222110000 +0000" stop="20250222113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Rescues Pearl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Pearl's efforts to snag Mr. Brewster seem doomed until he makes a ridiculous public proposal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222113000 +0000" stop="20250222120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Joins The Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed, who took a job as a garbage man to do something to keep busy, gets a job at the O.K. Oil Company on the Board of Directors after Drysdale talks him into it. He decides to help the company get more oil and money. The clan brings oil from their backyard to donate more oil, and to make some profit for O.K. Oil, they start an airline with the O.K. plane, complete with Jethro as the pilot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222120000 +0000" stop="20250222123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Double-cross Country Race, All’s Fair At The Fair, The Marry-go-round</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye competes in a cross-country auto race against an opponent who has a high-powered streamlined streak of a car., Bluto, the daring hot air balloon rider, catches the eye of Olive at a carnival, much to Popeye's chagrin., Popeye wants to propose to Olive, but can't work up the nerve. His fellow sailor, Shorty, helps him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222123000 +0000" stop="20250222130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tops With Pops, Drag-along Droopy, Tall In The Trap</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom accidentally grabs Tyke, Spike the bulldog's son, when he is trying to get to Jerry., Droopy is a shepherd but his sheep graze in cattle country which brings in the angry cattle owner., Jerry is a cheese rustler in the old west and Tom gets deputized to bring him to justice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222130000 +0000" stop="20250222140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>For The Love Of Pizza, The Rude Intruder, Charlie In Hot Water, How To Trap A Woodpecker, Goofy Gardener, Jungle Medics, Secret Weapon, Pecking Holes In Poles</sub-title>
    <desc>"In a take on the Little Red Riding Hood tale, Woody pauses as Miss Meany's grandmother in the hopes of eating the pizza she brought., Chilly and Maxie try to prevent a man from putting an oil well on top of their igloo., Charlie Beary attempts to fix the hot water tank himself., A woodsman tries to capture Woody to make a feather hat for his disgruntled wife., A butler tries to stop the gardener from disturbing the guests at a fancy party., Monkey medics help a lion with a tooth ache., Space Mouse goes under cover as a cat on Planet Feline to gather intel on an incoming cat invasion., A telephone company employee is sent out to capture Woody after he pecks holes in dozens of telephone poles."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222140000 +0000" stop="20250222150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Star Is Bored, Sheep Ahoy, Of Thee I Sting, Baton Bunny, Well Worn Daffy, Merlin The Magic Mouse, Knighty Knight Bugs</sub-title>
    <desc>"Daffy Duck is jealous of Bugs Bunny's stardom. He demands to be put into a film and lands a role as Bugs' stunt double. , Ralph the Wolf waits for the brief interlude between watchdogs before making off with a sheep; however, every attempt by Ralph is thwarted by Sam the Sheepdog. , A bunch of mosquitoes take lessons on how to attack a farmer. , Bugs takes on the unexpected role of being an orchestra conductor. , In the hot desert, Speedy Gonzales fights Daffy for water. , Merlin, the mouse, is performing a magic show for his one audience member, a cat. , Bugs is a hapless court jester who sneaks into the villain's castle while Black Knight Sam is snoozing. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222150000 +0000" stop="20250222160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Firebrand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>On a mission for President Grant, agent West travels to Fort Savage to meet with a Major Jason and help prevent a revolution in Canada that outlaw Shawn O'Riley has plans to incite. At the fort, West reads a description of O'Riley and realizes too late his striking resemblance to Major Jason. O'Riley announces that he now controls the fort and is holding the real major and his men captive. Meanwhile, Gordon has gone under cover to learn the details of the revolution. He arrives at West's side just as his partner is trapped on the wrong side of O'Riley's gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222160000 +0000" stop="20250222170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Alias Bill Hawks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill Hawks travels to a desert town to visit an old friend, an indian who has a ranch there. However, upon arriving on his friend's property, he discovers that it is under the control of the local townspeople, who are drilling for water, and that his friend is nowhere to be seen. The townspeople are unwilling to give him any information, and in fact display outright hostility towards him, leading Hawks to suspect that his friend may be in danger or even dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222170000 +0000" stop="20250222180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Barbary Red</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick is shanghaied at a saloon by a woman whom Jarrod once defended for that very crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222180000 +0000" stop="20250222190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Squaw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Fleeing from both Matt Dillon and his double-crossed partners, outlaw Gristy Calhoun discovers that his survival in the badlands depends on help from an indian woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222190000 +0000" stop="20250222200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Rebel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Cartwrights catch young Billy Penn trying to steal some of their cattle they try to set the young rustler on the straight and narrow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222200000 +0000" stop="20250222203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Lou Mallory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou Mallory has arrived in North Fork and quickly purchases land, which includes the hotel and Milly Scott's store. She pays higher prices than the sellers feel their properties are worth. Everyone is happy until they find out that Lou really is an astute businesswoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222203000 +0000" stop="20250222210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Night, Deadly Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Townspeople brace for the worst when a new girl arrives—with symptoms of smallpox.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222210000 +0000" stop="20250222220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Prophecy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The drovers have a Saturday off for the first time in a long time. Staying in a ghost town, Rowdy and his friend, Rabbit, shoot at a schoolhouse bell. A bullet ricochets and kills Jud Hilton. His brother, Brother William, a self-proclaimed minister, puts a curse on them and says they can't outrun death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222220000 +0000" stop="20250222223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Jenny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When Paladin is hired by a woman to discourage the advances of an unwanted suitor, it isn't long before she vanishes, the trail of clues leading to a group of counterfeiters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222223000 +0000" stop="20250222230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Reunion For A Revenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Several men escape from Yuma Prison with a thirst for revenge against a man named Aben Starr. He works at the Saddle Creek Way Station and Randall shows up there expecting the men to arrive also. Soon two of the escapees do arrive and take Josh and Starr captive while waiting for their partners to show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250222230000 +0000" stop="20250223010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Nutty But Nice, Sock-bye-baby, Three Little Twirps, Booby Dupes, Mutts To You, Spook Louder</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are singing waiters who are enlisted by a doctor to try and cheer up a little girl.  It seems that the girl's father is a banker who was kidnapped with $300,000 worth of bonds.  Failing to cheer up the girl, the Stooges go out looking for the father and by a series of coincidences wind up in the bad guys hideout.  The villains return and after a wild fight the boys free the missing man. , The Stooges mistakenly kidnap a baby they find on their doorstep.  When the cops and the baby's mother come looking for the baby, the boys panic and flee into the country with the cops (one of them is the baby's father) pursuing them by motorcycle.  It all ends happily with the baby reunited with its parents and the Stooges running off disguised as bushes. , The Stooges are left in charge of a spooky mansion, when an eccentric inventor goes to Washington with a death ray. , The Stooges get a job putting up posters for a circus but discover that instead of money, their pay is tickets to the show.  When trying to scalp their tickets gets them in trouble, they hide out backstage where Curly has an encounter with a bearded lady and Moe and Larry hide in a horse suit.  When they're caught, the circus manager gives them a choice of going to jail or joining the circus.  What they don't know is that they are to be targets for the Zulu spear thrower.  When Curly hits the spear thrower with one of his own spears, the boys are on the run once again. , The Stooges are three fish peddlers who decide to cut out the middleman by catching their own fish.  They trade their car and $300 for a "new" boat, which turns out to be a piece of junk that soon falls apart and sinks in the middle of the ocean.  Luckily the boys also have a rowboat, which they climb into and then try to signal some passing planes for help.  Unfortunately, their paint-spattered rag is mistaken for a Japanese flag and they are bombed from the sky. , When the stooges find a baby they take it back to their dog laundry business, but wind up in the dog house when they are accused of kidnapping the baby. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223010000 +0000" stop="20250223033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The War Of The Gargantuas</sub-title>
    <desc>"An experimental lab animal called a gargantua escapes from his captors and is suspected to be the creature that is killing people all over the countryside. But when the gargantua from the lab appears at the same time as the evil gargantua, the two begin to battle across Japan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223033000 +0000" stop="20250223040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Pop Goes The Joker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E57</episode-num>
    <desc>The Joker and a local artist team up after an act of spray paint vandalism. Batman and Robin await the Joker's next criminal move.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223040000 +0000" stop="20250223050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Empath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>On a planet doomed to destruction, Kirk, Spock and McCoy become involved with two aliens who use them as laboratory animals in a bizarre series of tests on an alien empath who may be the savior of her planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223050000 +0000" stop="20250223060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Energy Eater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A hospital is built on reclaimed land inhabited by the Native American bear-spirit legend Matchemonedo which threatens to destroy anyone who inhabits it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223060000 +0000" stop="20250223070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Collision Of Planets</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Robinson's come across a group of space hippies who are trying to destroy the planet the Robinson's currently inhabit. It is up to the Robinson's and Dr. Smith to stop them or they will all be doomed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223070000 +0000" stop="20250223080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Condemned</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>By presidential directive, Admiral Nelson and Commander Crane turn the Seaview over to a publicity seeking scientist who plans to break the crush barrier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223080000 +0000" stop="20250223090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Underground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings help out giants who are resisting the tyrannical Giant government.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223090000 +0000" stop="20250223100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Of Nero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1915, the travelers try to keep the ghost of Nero from taking revenge on a descendant of Nero's rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223100000 +0000" stop="20250223110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Beachhead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An architect's close encounter with a spaceship leads him to investigate a small town's hydroelectric plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223110000 +0000" stop="20250223120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Experiment</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt gets a cry for help from an unusual victim -- a dolphin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223120000 +0000" stop="20250223123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Zack Tapes   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack uses his subliminal advertising course to get Kelly to go with him to the Sweetheart Dance. But when his plan backfires, the whole school vies for his affection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223123000 +0000" stop="20250223130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Friendship Business   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang starts a business selling friendship bracelets, but Zack's tough work schedule tests the limits of their friendship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223130000 +0000" stop="20250223133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Close Encounters Of The Nerd Kind   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Looking for a way to make a quick buck, Slater and Zack have Screech dress up as an alien from outer space to trick a tabloid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223133000 +0000" stop="20250223140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Slater's Friend   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Slater unwittingly dooms his chameleon when he leaves it with Screech.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223140000 +0000" stop="20250223143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Save That Tiger   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack and Slater's prank war against rival school Valley High escalates, Screech gets kidnapped!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223143000 +0000" stop="20250223150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Screech's Birthday   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After the gang forgets Screech's birthday, he gets revenge by sending them all to detention, not knowing they're planning a surprise party in Mr. Belding's office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223150000 +0000" stop="20250223153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Career Fever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg writes a class paper about wanting to become an architect like his dad. Mike reads the paper and is ecstatic and encouraging, but is Greg's heart really in it?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223153000 +0000" stop="20250223160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Alice, Hello</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids begin to give Alice the cold shoulder treatment after she reveals that Greg and Peter broke an antique lamp of Carol's. The girls join the bandwagon when Alice innocently tells Carol that Marcia left the stereo on all night. Feeling unwanted and no longer needed, Alice quits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223160000 +0000" stop="20250223163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Richie's Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie buys a car from Fonzie and finds out that it is stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223163000 +0000" stop="20250223170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Monastery Show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne is allowed to stay at a convent for a couple of weeks, but she soon gets on the Mother Superior's bad side when she has trouble keeping a vow of silence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223170000 +0000" stop="20250223173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Rafe Hollister Sings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rafe Hollister, a simple farmer with an incredible voice, is encouraged by Andy to enter the Mayberry singing contest, much to the dismay of the mayor and other officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223173000 +0000" stop="20250223180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Moustache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy dislikes Ricky's new moustache. In order to make her grievance known, she glues a moustache and beard on to her face. Then, Ricky agrees to shave his moustache off, as long as Lucy gets rid of hers. Lucy tries to get the facial hair off, but is unsuccessful.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223180000 +0000" stop="20250223183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver learns he has to go to the dentist and that's when his friends tell him some horror stories about the drill the dentist is going to use. This prompts Beaver to become downright scared of going to the dentist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223183000 +0000" stop="20250223190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets Adopted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally wins a trophy at school and Beaver accidentally breaks it. This leads Ward to accuse Beaver of being jealous of Wally and that he broke it on purpose. Upset, Beaver decides to get new parents and heads to an adoption agency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223190000 +0000" stop="20250223193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Saves Drysdale's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When Pearl calls to yodel for him as a surprise, Jane suggests to Drysdale that he employs Pearl to be the head housekeeper, and when he suggests it to Pearl, she thinks he means marriage. And when Granny and Jed visit Mrs. Drysdale, who is going to a health spa, she says how Milburn is getting a more glamorous wife in her, but they think Drysdale is getting a brand new wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223193000 +0000" stop="20250223200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly's Animals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Elly's animals converge on the Clampett estate when Pearl starts giving yodeling lessons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223200000 +0000" stop="20250223203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Two On A Raft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An ill-fated three-hour tour aboard the S.S. Minnow shipwrecks seven castaways on a uncharted island. Gilligan and the Skipper set out on a flimsy raft to find civilization.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223203000 +0000" stop="20250223210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Home Sweet Hut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A hurricane is coming, so the castaways build a hut for all, but tensions mount and soon they all build their own huts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223210000 +0000" stop="20250223213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Key To The Crime  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Vint is accused of being a serial burglar after a break-in at the Harper house, Mama and Iola set out to prove his innocence and catch the real criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223213000 +0000" stop="20250223220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Up Is Hard To Do  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Finances not only cause Vint and Naomi to separate—but also force them to remain living at home with Mama.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223220000 +0000" stop="20250223230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Model Marriage / This Year's Model / Original Sin / Vogue Rogue / Too Clothes For Comfort (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A married pair of model agency owners clash over the use of one of their models has captured the captain's eye; Julie becomes a showstopper when she models in place of her beautiful model friend who has fallen in love; a cosmetics king searches for a unique woman to represent his new product; the daughter of a clothing manufacturer loses his latest line with the help of the man she loves."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223230000 +0000" stop="20250223233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Spoiled Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Arnold the spoiled kid moves to town, he thinks he can walk all over the townsfolk, including Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250223233000 +0000" stop="20250224000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Survivor- Jamie Knoll O'neill</sub-title>
    <desc>"A former Survivor contestant herself, Lisa Whelchel meets Jamie Knoll O’Neill, owner of her late father's Survivor collection, the best known in private hands.  Survivor Champion Ethan Zohn is today's expert and he's brought something to trade that is truly one of a kind vintage Survivor."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224000000 +0000" stop="20250224003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Once again, Hawkeye writes home to his father, telling him of the latest gossip: the camp gets a new surgeon, who turns out to be a fake; Hawkeye bets he can walk into the mess tent naked for lunch and no one will notice; and Radar cheats on his final exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224003000 +0000" stop="20250224010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Long-john Flap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp suffers from the severe cold, except for Hawkeye who has received some long johns from his father. They get passed around from person to person as a gift, a gambling stake, a trade, a bribe, stolen and given up to Father Mulcahy, who ends up giving them away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224010000 +0000" stop="20250224013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Stephanie's Conversion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Stephanie comes back from Sunday School, Rev. Chong visits Edith to tell her that even though she is welcome anytime at Sunday School, Stephanie is Jewish. Edith accepts it, unlike Archie. Selfishly, Archie decides to change Stephanie's religion but Edith interrupts that it's not his decision. So Edith brings Archie and herself to visit a Rabbi to get more information of the religion. 
Later that night, Stephanie awaits at the porch for the return of Edith and Archie. She and her uncle discuss and he approves that it's her decision and whatever religion she'll be, he'll love her the way he has.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224013000 +0000" stop="20250224020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Gets Fired</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When an ill woman tells Edith to let her die with dignity at the SunShine Home, the woman's family are furious after her death. The manager fires Edith for her selfishness, even though Edith honoured the woman's wish. Later that night, the woman's daughter thanks Edith to be with her mother as she passed away since she (the daughter) never got to visit her own mother back then.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224020000 +0000" stop="20250224023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Next Door</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Louise Jefferson returns for a visit at the Bunker's place to ask Edith if she can sell her (Louise's) former house. Edith doubts but Archie makes her agree so that they (mostly he) can choose white people to move in. When Edith sells the house to a couple and she invites the lady to her house, Archie realises that the woman is black and so is her husband. But Archie isn't disturbed when he finds out that the man is a cop, which could be good for Archie's safety.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224023000 +0000" stop="20250224030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Stephanie's Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Stephanie's father, Floyd, finally arrives with a devastating proposition for the Bunkers: They can keep Stephanie if they agree to pay him $1000 cash!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224030000 +0000" stop="20250224033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Soap To Nuts</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice plays monopoly with a bored Mama. Then, in Soap to Nuts, Carol's soap opera addiction threatens her marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224033000 +0000" stop="20250224040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Noisy Speech, The / Tv Commercials / Miss Nobody</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Noisy Speech, Harvey tries to deliver a speech but his noisy friends interrupt him. Then, in TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parody TV products, including Jay Detergent, Buffercin, One-A-Way Vitamin, Dear's Sigh-Hard Battery, Mellow Pages, American Depressed Credit Card, Braces, Dear's Sigh Hard, and A Salty Fish. Finally, in Miss Nobody, Carol can't get anyone's attention, even after she causes a mess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224040000 +0000" stop="20250224043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Letters From One Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A campaign to help Rob backfires when his program doesn't air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224043000 +0000" stop="20250224050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Pink Pills And Purple Parents</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The side effects of a special medication cause Laura to go loopy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224050000 +0000" stop="20250224053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Unconventional Behavior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed handcuffs himself to Ralph on their way to the Raccoon convention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224053000 +0000" stop="20250224060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Morrow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Before leaving on a 40-year mission, an astronaut meets a woman and they fall in love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224060000 +0000" stop="20250224070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Thirty-first Of February  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The passing away of Andrew Anderson's spouse sets off strange events calculated to drive the widower insane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224070000 +0000" stop="20250224080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Gitano (aka Toys)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When the young ruler of a small central European principality takes refuge after being deceived into thinking his regent intends to assassinate him, the IMF plots to "kidnap" the boy so as to remove him from the clutches of his real enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224080000 +0000" stop="20250224090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Storm Center</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a dock worker in Florida, Kimble is recognized by Marcie King, a young woman whom five years earlier asked Kimble to perform an abortion for her (illegal at the time; pre-Roe Vs. Wade). Kimble refused due to his religious beliefs, and Mar</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224090000 +0000" stop="20250224100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Ballinger's Choice</sub-title>
    <desc>"Illicit romance leads to murder as Harry Orwell follows the trail of a married publisher having an affair with a 16-year-old girl."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224100000 +0000" stop="20250224103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224103000 +0000" stop="20250224110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224110000 +0000" stop="20250224113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 125 -- Safe Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>There's been a rash of cracked safes in the area, and Malloy thinks the suspect is someone who lives in the neighborhood who now claims to be a reformed family man. In the meantime, he and Reed track down a female robbery suspect, who turns out to be a victim herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224113000 +0000" stop="20250224120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Extortion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy stares down the barrel of a rifle during the search for gloved robbers who are able to make off with $500 from a tavern in a stolen car. He and Reed also try to apprehend a group of anti-semites before their repeated shakedown attempts cause further damage to a defiant Holocaust survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224120000 +0000" stop="20250224130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Black History In Music</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill is going stir crazy from being cooped up all winter, so Toony suggests planning a vacation!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224130000 +0000" stop="20250224133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry become convinced that the Cooper house is haunted by a witch and Beaver and Larry are scared to death. So when June gets Beaver a job walking Mrs. Cooper's dog, Beaver's fear gets the best of him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224133000 +0000" stop="20250224140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus Ride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward allow Wally to escort Beaver on a bus headed to a friend's house in Crystal Falls. However, on one of the stops, Beaver inadvertently gets on the wrong bus, a bus that takes him back to Mayfield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224140000 +0000" stop="20250224150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dodging Domino</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Phil Schuyler is a two-bit songwriter who comes to a bad end on Halloween night. Someone enters his bungalow while Phil is taking a bath and tosses an electric heater into his tub.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224150000 +0000" stop="20250224160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Magician  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a night at the magic show with Julie, Matlock agrees to defend magician Daniel Fontaine when he's charged with the murder of his assistant and lover, Sandy Farrell, a woman who was as devious as she was beautiful.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224160000 +0000" stop="20250224170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Tear Down The Walls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A minister who was integrating his church(by inviting Virgil and Althea to attend services)is poisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224170000 +0000" stop="20250224180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Sinner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A young preacher, Matthew Fordwick (John Ritter), comes to Walton's Mountain fresh from seminary, where he has learned the currently-popular fire and brimstone style of preaching.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224180000 +0000" stop="20250224190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hiders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young teenager from a group of squatters decides he can do better than stealing, he changes his ways. But the leader of the squatters will try to manipulate the young man with the people who have treated him best.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224190000 +0000" stop="20250224200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Five Sundowns To Sunup</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A family embarks upon a kidnapping spree in an attempt to halt an execution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224200000 +0000" stop="20250224203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Never Rides Alone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunslinger rides into North Fork for a meeting with Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224203000 +0000" stop="20250224210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>I Take This Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou looks for a way out when the man her dying father promised her to arrives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224210000 +0000" stop="20250224220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Antone Rose Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>"Invalid rancher Henry Ludlow is so determined that daughter Judy not marry Basque sheepherder Antone Rose that he sells his land and joins the wagon train to head west. When Antone learns of this, he joins the train as well to marry her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224220000 +0000" stop="20250224230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Not Available</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The paramedics complain when a rule forbidding squads to cross each other's territories causes them to come late to an accident scene. An elderly woman is treated at the hospital. While transporting a non-vital patient, the paramedics respond to an auto accident. A prisoner breaks out of jail and gets trapped on a ledge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224230000 +0000" stop="20250224233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Army-navy Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp tunes into the Army/Navy football game, only to be shelled and have an unexploded bomb land in the middle of the compound. They ring around trying to identify the bomb, and the camp prepares for the worst. Hawkeye and Trapper are left the task of following instructions to disarm the bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250224233000 +0000" stop="20250225000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Frank argue over Frank's surgical ability. Hawkeye performs a difficult operation and the patient does not recover as he should. Hawkeye begins to doubt his ability and moves out of The Swamp. He decides to open up his patients again, and discovers a nick in the colon that even Frank admits anyone could have missed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225000000 +0000" stop="20250225003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Fred C. Dobbs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's normal drone of verbal abuse upsets Ginger, so Hawkeye puts his arm in a cast while he is asleep. Frank puts in for a transfer, and after Franks tells Margaret he's leaving, she decides to leave as well. As a result, Col. Blake puts both Hawk and Trap on double post-op duty until he finds replacements for Majs. Burns and Houlihan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225003000 +0000" stop="20250225010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cease-fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>General Clayton calls to say that a ceasefire is to be declared. The camp celebrates, Klinger gives away his dresses and locals start to take pieces of the camp. But Trapper does not believe it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225010000 +0000" stop="20250225013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Filling Station Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man is accused of being the mysterious crook who's been robbing Wally's filling station. Andy and Barney try to determine his guilt or innocence in a variety of methods.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225013000 +0000" stop="20250225020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Discovers America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie doesn't like his new teacher, "Old Lady Crump," because she gives too much homework. Andy comments on the teacher, words which Opie twists in his retelling to Ms. Crump, and she is furious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225020000 +0000" stop="20250225023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts In London</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are on the plane to England, with Sir Jethro as their leader. But with this comes a detour. The Clampetts get off the plane in San Francisco, after Jethro believes it is England. They get back on the plane and do finally arrive in England and are told that Jed’s cousin, Marcus, is late, meaning deceased, but they think he means late because he is diseased. After they arrive, Granny runs into trouble at the customs inspector’s office and gets her medical supplies and her jug confiscated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225023000 +0000" stop="20250225030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Visit From Cousin Goober</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Goober pays Gomer a surprise visit. Goober says he's through working at the filling station and wants to give the Marines a try for a week to see if he likes it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225030000 +0000" stop="20250225033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>D-day At Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan pulls a hoax to get a general to believe Klink is replacing him as chief of staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225033000 +0000" stop="20250225040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Schultz Meets Mata Hari</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets a female to pry information out of Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225040000 +0000" stop="20250225043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Peace Treaty</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Mama remembers her sister life. Then, in Peace Treaty, Japan and Russia try to sign a peace treaty but can't agree on anything.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225043000 +0000" stop="20250225053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spanish Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Jimmy Morrow can't seem to catch a break. Already on probation for car theft, he's charged with stealing a valuable Spanish cross and killing its owner. Mason feels sorry for the kid and decides to take the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225053500 +0000" stop="20250225060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Self-improvement Of Salvadore Ross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A man finds that he can trade anything he has, including youth and personality, with anybody else.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225060500 +0000" stop="20250225063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Kind Waitress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A waitress and her boyfriend plan the death of an elderly rich guest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225063500 +0000" stop="20250225070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Cheap Is Cheap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A miserly man is appalled to discover his wife is planning to spend his life's savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225070500 +0000" stop="20250225080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After one of Mannix's detective friends is murdered, he discovers the man worked for a mafioso and sets out to learn why he died, despite pressure to stop digging.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225080500 +0000" stop="20250225090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Duel In The Desert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Years earlier, Mel Danvers organized a successful hijacking and walked away with a cool million. But there is a witness: a stewardess. Danvers engineers a campaign of terror to keep her mum, until Cannon puts a stop to it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225090500 +0000" stop="20250225100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Little Glory, Little Death, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A blackmailing actress gets pushed off a cliff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250225100000 +0000" stop="20250225103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
