<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207080500 +0000" stop="20250207090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Proxy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man hires Cannon! The man's will requires than an investigator look into his death, so Christopher Grant hires Cannon to see if any of the man's scheming relatives might have helped him to an early exit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207090500 +0000" stop="20250207100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem For A Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of men pretending to be Barnaby and J.R. murder a writer employed by a publishing empire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207100000 +0000" stop="20250207103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Baseball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Police search for a safecracker who left his calling card at the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207103000 +0000" stop="20250207110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - The Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's cases range from purse snatching to homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207110000 +0000" stop="20250207113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 45 -- Bright Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy report to a burglary call that was witnessed by a boy with a photographic memory. Afterward, they are called to the scene of two drunk men shooting at a box of dynamite at close range in a residential area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207113000 +0000" stop="20250207120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 65 -- Cigarettes, Cars And Wild, Wild Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy help take down a chop-shop that employs cute girls in mini-skirts to steal cars from trusting men. They also arrest a young man who grows pot and holds parties in the home of his unsuspecting shut-in aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207120000 +0000" stop="20250207130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Black History In Tv &amp; Film</sub-title>
    <desc>"Legendary filmmaker Ayoka Chenzira joins Bill and Toony's celebration honoring the achievements of African Americans in TV &amp; Film."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207130000 +0000" stop="20250207133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An animal is chewing up June's flower bed, so Ward and the boys set a trap to catch it. They soon catch a white rabbit, which Beaver talks Ward and June into keeping. Beaver names him Henry only to later discover Henry is really a Henrietta and she's expecting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207133000 +0000" stop="20250207140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Runs Away</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry gets Beaver into trouble when he goads him into trying out Ward's drill. Discovering that the boys damaged the garage wall, Ward hits the roof and scolds Beaver, who in turn decides to run away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207140000 +0000" stop="20250207150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Angry Astronaut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Astronaut Matthew Heller is suspected of killing his old service rival, General Addison Brand, after Brand is put in charge of the astronaut program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207150000 +0000" stop="20250207160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Abduction  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock has every intention of preserving lawyer-client confidentiality, but when a group of mobsters kidnap Michelle to extort information from him, Matlock is forced to weigh his professional ethics against her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207160000 +0000" stop="20250207170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Necessary Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In this humorous episode Virgil and the Chief arrest a man for bigamy. It soon becomes a polygamy case after an endless parade of wives come to visit their husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207170000 +0000" stop="20250207180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Indiscretion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Corabeth finds a romantic letter in Ike's belongings and wants a divorce</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207180000 +0000" stop="20250207190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Matt Dillon Must Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A mountain family in an attempt to avenge the death of one of their own capture Matt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207190000 +0000" stop="20250207200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Jonah</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights hire a man who has a reputation for being cursed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207200000 +0000" stop="20250207203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Goodbye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubborn Grandpa Fogarty is Lucas's main roadblock as he tries to get young Woody Fogarty to attend school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207203000 +0000" stop="20250207210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Shattered Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark meet Mark Twain and find out that he hides a sad secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207210000 +0000" stop="20250207220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hollister John Garrison Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bitter alcoholic Stevenson Drake develops a dislike for the even tempered John Hollister, a fellow Southerner, when he learns he didn't fight for the Confederacy. He also is bothered by the friendliness between his wife and Hollister."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207220000 +0000" stop="20250207230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Communications</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A young worker gets his arm caught in a machine. A communication snafu occurs between Squad 51 and the hospital. Dr. Morton treats a young violinist. Two boys get a car trapped on the roof of a house. A woman tries to commit suicide by overdosing and won't let the paramedics treat her, making them wait until she passes out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207230000 +0000" stop="20250207233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester infuriates the camp when he hoards his stateside newspapers, and Hawkeye reunites two Korean brothers who have been fighting on opposite sides of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250207233000 +0000" stop="20250208000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Judgment: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The military police think they've solved a rash of thefts at the 4077th when they apprehend Klinger with Hawkeye's stolen camera.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208000000 +0000" stop="20250208003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snappier Judgment: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. and Hawkeye resolve to clear Klinger's name after he chooses Winchester to defend him at his military court-martial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208003000 +0000" stop="20250208010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>'twas The Day After Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To boost post-yuletide morale on Dec 26, Potter has the officers and enlisted men change places for the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208010000 +0000" stop="20250208013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three's A Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Every time Andy tries to be alone with Mary, Barney shows up. After Andy explains that he wants to be alone with her, Barney believes that Andy is planning to propose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208013000 +0000" stop="20250208020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bookie Barber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A bookie from Raleigh sets himself up in Floyd's barbershop as an extra barber, trying to avoid the heat. Andy gets suspicious when the new barber has the same three clients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208020000 +0000" stop="20250208023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Plays Solomon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny's plan to stop Pearl's yodeling backfires when the police she called find her illegal still.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208023000 +0000" stop="20250208030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer The M.p.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer ends up on MP duty, where one of his first feats is to mistakenly arrest a government inspector.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208030000 +0000" stop="20250208033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Tanks For The Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to photograph and destroy a model for a radio-controlled tank that is being tested at camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208033000 +0000" stop="20250208040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Adolf Please Stand Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>With camp security raised, Hogan and his men are desperate to smuggle top-secret German fortifications information to the Allies. The solution? Make liberal use of Carter's remarkable impersonation of Adolf Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208040000 +0000" stop="20250208043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Sammy Davis Jr.</sub-title>
    <desc>In Backstage, Carol reunites with an old friend and her old prejudices come back. Then, in No Frills Airline, Tim receives horrible airplane service all because he didn't pay an extra fee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208043000 +0000" stop="20250208053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Romantic Rogue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After con man Stacey Chandler and Helen Harvey are married in Vegas, Chandler's former associate and scheming con woman, Irene Wallace, is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208053500 +0000" stop="20250208060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>In Praise Of Pip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An alcoholic bookie regrets that he wasn't a better father to his son, Pip, critically wounded in South Vietnam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208060500 +0000" stop="20250208063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Interrupt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A little boy on a train tries desperately to tell someone a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208063500 +0000" stop="20250208070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Crooked Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple passing through a small town falls victim to its crooked officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208070500 +0000" stop="20250208080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Fine Day For Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>One might think that after waking from a year-long coma, the worst would be in the past. But that is not true for Mannix's client, injured in a hit-and-run accident and now the target of killers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208080500 +0000" stop="20250208090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Night Flight To Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A man hires Cannon to find out who is using trained dogs to kill the man he served with in Vietnam, and why. It might have something to do with the unit's commanding officer, permanently disabled, perhaps by his own men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208090500 +0000" stop="20250208100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A sportsman's plans for a new life begin with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208100000 +0000" stop="20250208103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Betty Jo's Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo Elliott starts a day nursery to augment the family income.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208103000 +0000" stop="20250208110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Spur Line To Shady Rest: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The C&amp;W Railroad sends a troubleshooter, Homer Bedloe, to Hooterville to see why the main line and the branch line do not connect to each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208110000 +0000" stop="20250208113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Hot-rod Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro wants a new car, embarrassed by the truck. He buys two new cars for two different images he is trying. But Jed tells him to just get a few new parts for the truck. Granny, who is celebrating her birthday, believes that they are planning to replace her. But she learns the truth, and wants the truck to stay the way it was. Jethro ends up getting a whole new front for the truck, and when Jed tells him to fix it, he gets a whole new back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208113000 +0000" stop="20250208120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Badger Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl shows up at the Clampett mansion, claiming she is a friend from back home, Emaline Fetty. The Clampetts welcome her into their house. But it turns out that Emaline is working with someone to blackmail the Clampetts. She takes pictures of her and Jed in a compromising position. Colonel Foxhall, the man who is in control of the caper, and Emaline develop the photos and show them to Jane and Drysdale, who believe something else is going on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208120000 +0000" stop="20250208123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Rodeo Romeo, Cartoons Ain’t Human, Royal Four Flusher</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Olive becomes enamored with cowboy Bluto at the rodeo, Popeye uses spinach to beat him in all the events., Popeye creates his own cartoon idea and casts himself as the hero and Olive as the heroine in a spoof of an old-fashioned melodrama., Bluto the Magician steal Olive away from Popeye in the park."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208123000 +0000" stop="20250208130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Love Me Love My Mouse, The Alley Cat, Tom And Cherie</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom falls in love and offers Jerry as a gift for the female cat but things turn a little unexpected when she lends a sympathetic ear to his plight., An alley cat's romance is thwarted by a bulldog., Jerry needs a young mousketeer to be an errand boy to get to his love but Tom stands in his way."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208130000 +0000" stop="20250208140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Janie Get Your Gun, Hay Rube, Bear And The Bees, The Hollywood Matador, Gooney's Goofy Landings, Three Lazy Mice, Phoney Pony</sub-title>
    <desc>"An outlaw pastes Woody's face over his on his wanted poster. Calamity Jane goes after Woody, but then falls in love with the real outlaw when she sees what he really looks like., Sugarfoot falls in love with a circus horse named Starbrite and ends up fighting with a trainer he sees beating her., Cupid tries to help Fatso the Bear win over a lady bear., Woody is a matador fighting a bull named Oxnar the Terrible., Chilly and Maxie teach Gooney to make more graceful landings., Three lazy mice try to get out of working by claiming to be blind., Woody and Sugarfoot attempt to recapture two escaped thieves. The thieves disguise themselves as a horse with which Sugarfoot falls in love."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208140000 +0000" stop="20250208150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Hare Splitter, For Scent-imental Reasons, The Stupid Cupid, The Grey Hounded Hare, Honey's Money, Of Rice And Hen, Rabbit Romeo</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs and his neighbor rabbit, Casbah, compete for Daisy Lou's affection. , Pepe LePew walks into a perfume shop to sniff the various perfumes. The shopkeeper recruits a cat to fight him off, but Pepe ends up falling in love with the cat when it picks up a white stripe., Daffy gets hit by Elmer Fudd’s Cupid arrow. , Bugs goes to the racing track and fools around with the racing dogs. When the race starts, he gets the hounds to run off the track, get in a taxi cab, and sent off to the pound. , Sam marries an ugly, mean widow for her money. , Miss Prissy falls in love with Foggy when he’s the only one to treat her kindly. , Elmer's uncle, Judd, promises him $500 if he will watch his lovesick rabbit, Millicent. When Elmer gets Bugs to come over and keep Millie company, crazy things start happening."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208150000 +0000" stop="20250208160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Bogus Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Loveless is back with another plan to take over the world. This time he is using mock-ups of the treasury, prisons and armories to train his men to be able to take over these resources upon his command. After gaining control, Loveless will be instituted as dictator. However, his plan to get rid of West and Gordon goes foul and soon the agents are in hot pursuit of the little villain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208160000 +0000" stop="20250208170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lily Legend Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>"While riding through the desert plains, Duke and Charlie come across a sheriff as he is about to die of a heart attack and his female prisoner, Lily Legend, a childhood sweetheart of Duke who the sheriff is taking to be hanged for murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208170000 +0000" stop="20250208180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher Of Outlaws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria is kidnapped by outlaws who think she’s the local schoolteacher. The reason is unusual: The gang leader wants her to teach him how to read.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208180000 +0000" stop="20250208190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>A Town In Chains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of bandits attempt to rob a town while masquerading as soldiers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208190000 +0000" stop="20250208200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Spotlight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Viveca Lindfors guest stars as long-retired opera diva Angela Drake. Appointed entertainment committee chairman of the Virginia City anniversary celebration, Ben persuades Angela to come out of retirement for a command performance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208200000 +0000" stop="20250208203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Gun From Tucson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to stop embittered John Holliver from venting his wrath on the people who expelled him from town years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208203000 +0000" stop="20250208210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The High Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas becomes the target of a vengeful mountaineer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208210000 +0000" stop="20250208220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Two Graves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Wish volunteers Rowdy to fight Jeremiah O'Neal for money. O'Neal gives the fight away and Rowdy wins $50. The losers are ready to tar and feather O'Neal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208220000 +0000" stop="20250208223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Badman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Cynthia Palmer hires Paladin to clean up the town of Cedar Wells and get a gang out. She also wants him to send her schoolteacher nephew named Laredo back east. Paladin decides he can restore Laredo's self-respect and get rid of the gang at the same time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208223000 +0000" stop="20250208230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Six-up To Bannach</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh needs a ride to Brannach fast in order to stop an unjust hanging. The only mode of transportation available is a coach carrying a load of dynamite with a surly driver who doesn't take well to Josh. After the driver reluctantly agrees to allow Josh and his prisoner to travel with him, they encounter a number of obstacles along the way that slow them down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250208230000 +0000" stop="20250209010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Men In Black, A Ducking They Did Go, Idle Roomers, Micro-phonies, A Bird In The Head, Dizzy Detectives</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges become doctors at a large hospital where they disrupt patients and staff alike.   , After recruiting the police chief, governor and mayor into what turns out to be a sham duck hunting club, the Stooges cleverly find a way to avoid jail.  , The Stooges are carpenters who become policemen.  A mysterious burglar disguised as a gorilla has the cops baffled and Mr. Dill, the head of the citizens league, threatening the police chief's job.  The boys go on the case and pose as night watchmen at an antiques store.  They confront the crook, who turns out to be a real gorilla owned by Dill.  After defeating Dill and some other bad guys in a wild fight, the gorilla drinks some nitroglycerin and blows up. , The Stooges are working as bellboys in a large hotel when a side show promoter shows up with 'Lupe', a wild wolfman who promptly escapes.  The Stooges try to capture the wolfman by playing music to calm him, but music makes the wolfman go berserk and soon the Stooges are the ones trying to run away.  The boys end up caught in an elevator with the wolfman who shoots them into the sky. , The Stooges are working in a radio station where a pretty girl has just made a recording of "Voices of Spring" under an assumed name.  She wants to hide her singing career from her disapproving society parents while auditioning for Mrs. Bixby's "Krispy Krunchy" radio program.  After a run-in with a pompous violinist, the boys find the record and Curly starts mimicking to it, dressed as a women.  Mrs. Bixby witnesses their performance and is impressed enough to hire "Senorita Cucaracha" (Curly) and Senors "Mucho" and "Gusto" (Moe and Larry) for her radio program.  The boys show up in their disguises to "sing" at a Mrs. Bixby's party but run into trouble when Moe smashes the record over Curly's head.  The real singer tries to help by singing from behind a curtain while Curly mimics, but she is discovered and the Stooges exit to a hail of phonograph records. , The maniacal masters of madcap are back, digitally remastered, repackaged and hilarious as ever. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209010000 +0000" stop="20250209033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Curse Of The Werewolf</sub-title>
    <desc>"This British adaptation based on the novel The Werewolf of Paris by Guy Endore is brutal cult horror favorite that casts Oliver Reed as a young 18th-century Spaniard who has an adverse reaction to the full moon."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209033000 +0000" stop="20250209040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Ring Around The Riddler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler attempts to control prize fighting by brainwashing the current champ into throwing the next fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209040000 +0000" stop="20250209050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Wink Of An Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Members of a landing party investigating planet Scalos begin to vanish one by one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209050000 +0000" stop="20250209060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Spanish Moss Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A dreaming host conjures up the Creole legend of Père Malfait ("Father of Evil"), a moss-monster willing to kill anyone who threatens its survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209060000 +0000" stop="20250209070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted Lighthouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Robinsons leave the planet with an alien boy, J-5, in tow, promising to take the boy to his home planet. However, matters are complicated when the Robinsons think they have discovered a way back to Earth, one that would require breaking their promise to the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209070000 +0000" stop="20250209080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Admiral Nelson and Commander Crane become the prisoners of foreign scientists who convert them into bitter enemies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209080000 +0000" stop="20250209090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Ghost Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A Giant eccentric builds a Earthling-sized village, but when the Earthlings stumble into it, the man's sadistic daughter decides to have fun with her new "playthings."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209090000 +0000" stop="20250209100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Kill Two By Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug are hunted by two officers on a Japanese-held island in 1945.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209100000 +0000" stop="20250209110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Pursued</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An alien reaches out to Vincent with the intention of defecting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209110000 +0000" stop="20250209120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Road Rebels</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt joins a gang to stop jewel thieves connected to car robberies."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209120000 +0000" stop="20250209123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Lisa Card   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Lisa splurges with her dad's credit card, she asks the Bayside gang to help get the money back before her dad discovers the shopping spree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209123000 +0000" stop="20250209130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Election   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack finds out the Class President wins a trip to Washington, D.C., and campaigns hard against Jessie. But when the trip is canceled, he must campaign even harder to lose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209130000 +0000" stop="20250209133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Aloha Slater   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Slater is torn when his Army father tells him they're moving away. Jealous the spotlight's not on him, Zack spreads a rumor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209133000 +0000" stop="20250209140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing To The Max   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a dance contest is held at The Max, the gang splits off into pairs—Kelly and Slater, Zack and Jessie, and even Lisa and Screech!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209140000 +0000" stop="20250209143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Love Machine   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie becomes alarmed at the presence of Slater's old flame, especially when Screech's "love machine" shows that both Slater and his ex still have feelings for each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209143000 +0000" stop="20250209150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Isn't It Romantic   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>On Valentine's Day, the gang flashes back to the romantic adventures they've had in the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209150000 +0000" stop="20250209153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Going, Going... Steady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia comes home from school in a daydream and the rest of the family can't figure out her problem. It seems Marcia has a crush on a boy who doesn't even know she's alive, at least not until she studies up on his favorite hobby, insect collecting. The next time she comes home from school, she has exciting news, he asked her to "go steady."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209153000 +0000" stop="20250209160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Cyrano De Brady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter falls for Jan's friend Kerry, but needs Greg's worldly advice. Greg plays Cyrano for Peter, causing Kerry to think that it's Greg who has feelings for her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209160000 +0000" stop="20250209163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Richie Moves Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie feels that he doesn't have enough privacy, so he decides to move in with Chuck. He quickly discovers, though, that bachelor life isn't quite what he expected.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209163000 +0000" stop="20250209170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Squiggy In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When Squiggy begins dating a beautiful woman, Laverne and Shirley know they must break the news to him that he's being used.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209170000 +0000" stop="20250209173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Girlfriend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Helen's very pretty and very athletic niece comes to Mayberry for a visit. While she has a crush on Opie, she beats him in every sport they play, forcing her to turn to Aunt Helen for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209173000 +0000" stop="20250209180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Sentimental Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy and Ricky want to spend their 13th wedding anniversary alone, but the Mertzes have another idea: a surprise party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209180000 +0000" stop="20250209183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother's Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An 8th grade dance has Wally being pressured into attending with a girl, instead of going stag with Eddie. However, Mary Ellen Rogers becomes determined to have Wally take her and goes through Beaver to get to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209183000 +0000" stop="20250209190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's First Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A party is being thrown at the dancing school where Beaver and Wally once took lessons and they're both invited. This prompts Beaver to ask one particular girl who caught his eye, Betsy Patterson, if he could escort her to the dance. However, once at the dance, he finds that Betsy has promised other boys that she would dance with them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209190000 +0000" stop="20250209193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl From Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick arrives with his daughter, Essiebelle. He found love letters Jethro wrote to his daughter, a beauty contest winner. He plans to get Jethro and Essiebelle married so he can get his paws in the Clampett fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209193000 +0000" stop="20250209200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Play Cupid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is hoping that Elly May and Dash Riprock will settle down and get married, since the two have been out on a lot of dates. Dash is hoping to get a more serious relationship with Elly as well, but her family keeps getting in the way. But Elly is not looking for a future with the Hollywood movie star; she’d rather have a farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209200000 +0000" stop="20250209203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Gilligan's Mother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A native family from another island comes seeking a husband for their lovely but large daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209203000 +0000" stop="20250209210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Lovey's Secret Admirer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Howell starts receiving mysterious love notes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209210000 +0000" stop="20250209213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>My Phony Valentine  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama claims to have a date for Valentine's Day, Iola hires an escort—and it's painfully obvious that he's an escort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209213000 +0000" stop="20250209220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Bubba's Double Date  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Bubba's date for the prom cancels at the last minute, Mama fixes him up with Iola's shy, homely niece, Vernette.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209220000 +0000" stop="20250209230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Computerman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A slick computer matchmaker proceeds to pair up cruise guests while setting himself up with Julie; two American gold-diggers pretend to be French; a New York advertising executive meets up with a long-lost love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209230000 +0000" stop="20250209233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Prisoner Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady prisoner woos Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250209233000 +0000" stop="20250210000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Theme Parks- Morgan Richardson</sub-title>
    <desc>"Collector Morgan Richardson not only designs theme parks, he collectes all things theme park related.  Disney and pop culture Expert Joel Magee joins Lisa to appraise Morgan's fantastic collection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210000000 +0000" stop="20250210003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Follies Of The Living - Concerns Of The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While suffering a fever, Klinger communicates with the spirit of a dead soldier, Private Weston, who stays on to witness his own last rites.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210003000 +0000" stop="20250210010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Birthday Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret's birthday plans are spoiled when she and Klinger get stranded on a desolate roadside. Meanwhile, Charles gives a lecture for Margaret, and the surgeons assist in the delivery of a calf.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210010000 +0000" stop="20250210013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>California, Here We Come (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Separation is Archie's reaction when he discovers that Gloria has been unfaithful to her husband. For the first time in nine years, he turns his back on his daughter and sides with Michael.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210013000 +0000" stop="20250210020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie And The Superbowl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's Place is robbed on Superbowl Sunday, the busiest day of the year.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210020000 +0000" stop="20250210023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At The Pta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Edith develops laryngitis on the eve of her singing debut at Stephanie's PTA recital, Archie steps in to understudy the duet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210023000 +0000" stop="20250210030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Girl Like Edith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Edith invites butcher Klemmer and his new sweetheart, a Russian who is the spitting image of Edith, she notices that Klemmer might have the hots for Edith and not for her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210030000 +0000" stop="20250210033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Neil Sedaka</sub-title>
    <desc>In I.R.S. Office, Harvey uses his income tax tricks to woo a woman. Then, in Kitchen Commercials, Carol and the gang parody TV kitchen products. Finally, in The Long Goodnight, Carol tries to get rid of guests who have worn out their welcome.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210033000 +0000" stop="20250210040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Roddy Mcdowall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Laughter Is the Best Medicine, Carol can't control her laughter while Harvey attempts to propose. Then, in Assembly Line, Carol tells her husband she wants a divorce while at work in the factory. Finally, in The Little Foxes, a film parody, Carol plays Bette Davis, a woman hoping her husband will die so she can inherit his fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210040000 +0000" stop="20250210043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Emperor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob is offered a job at a men's magazine but Laura doesn't like the idea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210043000 +0000" stop="20250210050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Romances, Roses, And Rye Bread</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sally finds love in an unexpected place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210050000 +0000" stop="20250210053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>On Stage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, Alice and Ed are in a Raccoon play, and Ralph expects to be a big star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210053000 +0000" stop="20250210060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Steel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Boxing robot "Battling Maxo" breaks down before a match, forcing its manager to take its place in the ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210060000 +0000" stop="20250210070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Bonfire  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Preacher Robert Evans will go to murderous lengths to obtain a woman's manor for his gospel sanctuary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210070000 +0000" stop="20250210080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Falcon: Part 3</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Paris survives the explosion but his cover (and his mask) is blown. Meanwhile, Sabattini has taken Jim to the imprisoned Stephan. A hidden Barney has placed a hidden projector screen in Stephan's cell while Jim has a projector in his briefcase. They create an optical illusion and are able to free Stephan from his cell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210080000 +0000" stop="20250210090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Never Stop Running</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a migrant worker in New Mexico, Kimble becomes an unwilling party to the kidnapping of a young boy whom is the son of his landowner boss. The boy, Jimmie, has been abducted by Ralph Simmons, a disgruntled former football player, along wit</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210090000 +0000" stop="20250210100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Eyewitness</sub-title>
    <desc>"A slaying in a black ghetto finds Harry Orwell relying on a blind "eyewitness" to zero in on the killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210100000 +0000" stop="20250210103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Lsd Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Joe Friday and his partner, Bill Gannon, encounter a freaked-out young LSD user. This is the famous "Blue Boy" episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210103000 +0000" stop="20250210110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Explosion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A neo-Nazi psycho has planted a bomb somewhere in L.A. Friday and Gannon have to find it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210110000 +0000" stop="20250210113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 55 -- Missing Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After responding to a gas leak in a home, reed and malloy search for a missing child. Finally, they investigate an attempted car theft that ended with a fatal shooting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210113000 +0000" stop="20250210120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 75: Have A Nice Weekend</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers investigate robberies, attempted arson and a violent argument."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210120000 +0000" stop="20250210130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>For The Love Of Cartoons</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toon In With Me's Love Week celebration begins!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210130000 +0000" stop="20250210133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is all excited to have his friend, Larry Mondello, stay over for the weekend. However, things start off on the wrong foot when Beaver and Larry get into a fight, which ends with Beaver punching Larry in the stomach.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210133000 +0000" stop="20250210140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Cat Out Of The Bag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>The neighbors are going away for the weekend and Beaver and Wally have been put in charge of taking care of their lawn and their cat, Puff Puff. When Eddie shows up with his dog, Wolf, chaos erupts and Wolf chases Puff Puff away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210140000 +0000" stop="20250210150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Borrowed Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby mysteriously appears in Mason's office along with a rare St. Christopher medal, which could help identify the baby's parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210150000 +0000" stop="20250210160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Awesome  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Conrad asks Matlock to defend Anne Johnson when she's charged with the murder of her cheating ex-boyfriend, Dwayne Meeks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210160000 +0000" stop="20250210170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>...and Then You Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The Sparta police search for a killer and his girlfriend. But the case becomes personal when they take Althea and the grandson of one of the victims hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210170000 +0000" stop="20250210180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Heartache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose and Stanley plan to get married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210180000 +0000" stop="20250210190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Guns Of Cibola Blanca: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc and fellow stage passenger, Lyla, are captured by renegade Comancheros.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210190000 +0000" stop="20250210200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Patchwork Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Grant Williams (best known for his star turn in the classic sci-fi film 'The Incredible Shrinking Man') is cast as Albert "Patch" Saunders, a self-deprecating loner living in a ghost town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210200000 +0000" stop="20250210203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Friend In Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finds himself the unwilling companion of gunman Carl Avery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210203000 +0000" stop="20250210210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Skull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for escape after he's captured by outlaws while seeking help for an injured Mark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210210000 +0000" stop="20250210220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sara Proctor Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>"When children's dolls are found mutilated in her possession, passengers believe that Sara Proctor is either deranged or practicing witchcraft. Hale slowly arrives at the real story after Sara confides to him and Charlie's snooping."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210220000 +0000" stop="20250210230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>To Buy Or Not To Buy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy thinks about buying a house, but delays too long. Responding to a fire, the firemen find two children trapped on the second floor. Two driving students are involved in a minor collision. Another traffic accident results in two injuries and a missing dog. A teenage epileptic is stranded on a concrete beam under a bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210230000 +0000" stop="20250210233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood And Guts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is outraged when a sensationalistic war correspondent, Clayton Kibbee, reports irresponsible G.I. stunts as tales of military valor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250210233000 +0000" stop="20250211000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Holy Mess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An AWOL soldier, Nick Gillis, seeks sanctuary in the mess tent, after Father Mulcahy's service. At the same time, a special Sunday brunch is due to be served, following the donation of some eggs to the camp by a grateful farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211000000 +0000" stop="20250211003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth Shall Set You Free</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles has a serious toothache, but hates the thought of having anything done about it. The doctors suspect prejudice when an inordinate number of black casualties are brought in from a single unit, led by Major Weems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211003000 +0000" stop="20250211010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Points</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter sends for Sidney Freedman when he loses confidence in his surgical abilities, and Winchester loses patience with his bunkmates' sloppiness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211010000 +0000" stop="20250211013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy On Trial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A news mogul swears revenge on Andy after he is arrested for what he deems a minor infraction. In retaliation, he sends a reporter to Mayberry to dig up whatever dirt she can on Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211013000 +0000" stop="20250211020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Virgil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to help out his visiting cousin, Virgil. When Virgil makes one too many mistakes, Barney rails against him and storms out. Leave it to Andy to put things right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211020000 +0000" stop="20250211023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Duke Steals A Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke, Jed's bloodhound, becomes matchmaker for his master and a glamorous Frenchwoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211023000 +0000" stop="20250211030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Pfc Gomer Pyle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter postpones his vacation until all his men pass their Private First Class exams. Gomer, unfortunately, is the only one to fail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211030000 +0000" stop="20250211033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Forget To Write</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink fails a physical and gets combat duty at the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211033000 +0000" stop="20250211040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Rocket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to detour the German bombers that normally attack London to a nearby Allied airbase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211040000 +0000" stop="20250211043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Hollow Hero, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice has a flashback to when she first started dating her husband. Then, in The Hollow Hero, a guard refuses to the King and Queen inside without first receiving a popsicle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211043000 +0000" stop="20250211053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crimson Kiss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fay Allison is getting married in a few days to Dane Grover. Her roommate, Anita Bonsal, is having a clandestine affair with a married man, Carver Clement. When Aunt Louise arrives early one morning to see Fay, she finds Fay and Anita both unconscious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211053500 +0000" stop="20250211060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare At 20,000 Feet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While aboard a commercial aircraft, a man believes he is seeing a gremlin on its wing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211060500 +0000" stop="20250211063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The $2,000,000 Defense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate man makes a deal with his defense lawyer in order to get acquitted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211063500 +0000" stop="20250211070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Design For Loving</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plots to get away from his wife for a while without her knowing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211070500 +0000" stop="20250211080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Walk On The Blind Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Syndicate thugs have kidnapped an informer—or so they believe. Their victim is actually Peggy Fair, Mannix's secretary, which puts the detective on their trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211080500 +0000" stop="20250211090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Come Watch Me Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A mob killer murders Cannon's client. But the killer is someone Cannon will never suspect, and that leaves him unprepared when he is accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211090500 +0000" stop="20250211100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sunday: Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby engages in a game of cat-and-mouse with a murderer who blames him for his jail time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211100000 +0000" stop="20250211103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Kidnapping</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon help an employee rescue her kidnapped boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211103000 +0000" stop="20250211110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Interrogation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A new officer has been arrested for robbing a liquor store while on an undercover assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211110000 +0000" stop="20250211113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 105 -- Elegy For A Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Malloy pays tribute to Officer Tom Porter, who has recently fallen in the line of duty. Malloy recounts the close friendship they developed while training at the academy, as well as the moments where they crossed paths on duty, including the night of the officer's unfortunate demise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211113000 +0000" stop="20250211120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 25 -- Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed hunt down a suspect who has been bombing downtown storefronts. Then they report to a scuffle between two native americans at a bar that the bartender thinks may be a prelude to something a lot more serious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211120000 +0000" stop="20250211130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Love Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony set sail on a couples cruise."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211130000 +0000" stop="20250211133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Poem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes to Ward for help on the night before a poetry assignment is due. This prompts Ward to totally take over the project and write the whole poem himself. Things get complicated when Beaver wins an award for the poem and Ward is faced with explaining the truth to Beaver's principal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211133000 +0000" stop="20250211140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A school dance has Eddie swooning over his so-called "girl," Caroline. However, it's obvious Eddie has made up their relationship when Wally and him visit her and she instantly becomes smitten with Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211140000 +0000" stop="20250211150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Counterfeit Crank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man, his dead nephew and a military base are tangled up in a confusing case for Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211150000 +0000" stop="20250211160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Evening News: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Office pranks get out of hand—and may have led to murder. Matlock takes the case of Billy Finley, a recently fired office employee charged in the murder of another pink-slip recipient.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211160000 +0000" stop="20250211170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Look Back: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A copycat recreates a shocking unsolved murder from the past. Gillespie feels threatened after Ted Marcus suggests that Virgil should become the Chief. The situation becomes more tense after Virgil criticizes Parker and Bubba's actions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211170000 +0000" stop="20250211180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Lumberjack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A new company starts in the area and wants to sell wood to the Waltons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211180000 +0000" stop="20250211190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Guns Of Cibola Blanca: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt, Festus and Newly attempt to rescue Doc and Lyla from Shindrow's camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211190000 +0000" stop="20250211200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Debt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wiley and Annie Kane arrive at the Ponderosa to work off their father's debt to Ben. It seems as though the elder Kane once swindled the Cartwright patriarch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211200000 +0000" stop="20250211203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Queen-to-be of France hides out in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211203000 +0000" stop="20250211210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gunfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah has an infamous outlaw, Charlie Gordo, in his jail waiting for the U.S. marshal from Denver to take Gordo to the Yuma prison for hanging. With the arrival of the stage, Micah finds that the lawman has been killed, and he has to look to his friends to defend the jail from Gordo's gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211210000 +0000" stop="20250211220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Emmett Lawton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke Shannon stops in the town High Times and almost right away gets into a fight with, and accidentally kills, one of the gunmen who are essentially holding the town hostage. Then he finds his horse missing and ignores advise to leave."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211220000 +0000" stop="20250211230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Right At Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Brackett rides along with a fire department helicopter crew. A boy causes trouble for the paramedics when he and his father are rescued after their camper has overturned in a canyon. Dr. Early treats a boy with spinal meningitis. The firemen rescue a man from a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211230000 +0000" stop="20250211233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's A Will, There's A War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye goes to help at an aid station, and under heavy shelling he draws up a will, leaving various items to his friends at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250211233000 +0000" stop="20250212000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Promotion Commotion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester, Pierce and Hunnicutt find themselves in the sticky position of having to decide which enlisted men to recommend for promotion. For Winchester it could be a matter of life and death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212000000 +0000" stop="20250212003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heroes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is the golden boy of the world press when he treats a celebrity prizefighter, "Gentleman" Joe Cavanaugh, who has a stroke at the 4077th. Father Mulcahy finds the news hard to take, as Cavanaugh was a hero of his.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212003000 +0000" stop="20250212010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sons And Bowlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing to the Marines once again, Colonel Potter wishes there was one sport the 4077th were any good at. When Klinger mentions he can bowl, the Colonel decides to have a bowling competition. Unfortunately, he and Klinger are the only two good bowlers in the camp, so BJ and Father Mulcahy are "recruited" to the team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212010000 +0000" stop="20250212013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Deputy Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has been writing letters to his brother and sister-in-law for some time on courthouse stationary. Because of this, they have come to believe that he is a deputy, something they expect to see on their upcoming visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212013000 +0000" stop="20250212020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Mcbeevee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While walking through the woods, Opie meets Mr. McBeevee, a man who, Opie claims, "lives in the trees" and "jingles when he walks." Andy eventually learns that Opie's new friend works for the telephone company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212020000 +0000" stop="20250212023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Buys The Freeway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A confidence man tries to sell Jed the Hollywood Bowl, Griffith Park and the Hollywood Freeway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212023000 +0000" stop="20250212030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Third Finger, Left Loaf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is asked to be the best man at his friend's wedding. The night before the ceremony, he loses the ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212030000 +0000" stop="20250212033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Information Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After detecting an information leak in the area of Stalag 13, the Germans replace Klink with a more efficient officer, who Hogan sets up to take the fall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212033000 +0000" stop="20250212040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Art For Hogan's Sake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a French painting from ending up in Goering's art collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212040000 +0000" stop="20250212043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Openers / Jacques Touteaux / Fortune Cookies</sub-title>
    <desc>In Easy Openers, a hungry Carol tries to open her food locked in its container. Then, in Jacques Touteaux, Harvey describes the great feats Tim the diver will do, only he's too scared to do them. Finally, in Fortune Cookies, Carol suspects her best friend and husband are cheating together after a fortune cookie tells her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212043000 +0000" stop="20250212053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Vagabond Vixen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hollywood producer John Addison picks up an attractive young hitchhiker. Far from innocent, she turns out to be a blackmailer and a witness to a murder with which Addison is charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212053500 +0000" stop="20250212060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Kind Of A Stopwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is given a stopwatch that allows him to halt time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212060500 +0000" stop="20250212063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Man With A Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A man stands on the ledge of a hotel while police try to talk to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212063500 +0000" stop="20250212070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Safety For The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A man witnesses a murder by two gangsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212070500 +0000" stop="20250212080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Green Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When a counterfeiter disappears, Mannix is up against Federal agents as well as criminals who want the man's flawless plates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212080500 +0000" stop="20250212090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Alibi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon tries to extract reporter Peggy Angel from a clever frame. Who is the real murderer, and why frame this particular person?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212090500 +0000" stop="20250212100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Murdering Class, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a murder at a prep-school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212100000 +0000" stop="20250212103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Masked Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Four bandits wearing red masks commit a series of robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212103000 +0000" stop="20250212110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Examiner Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Two con men, posing as bank examiners, are bilking the elderly out of their life savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212110000 +0000" stop="20250212113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 135 -- Arson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In what would prove to be a very busy shift, Malloy and Reed search for a serial arsonist who spawns a copycat, settle a domestic dispute that results from a love triangle, rescue a man who wandered onto the ledge of a high rise and deal with a mentally ill man who is holding his wife at knife-point.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212113000 +0000" stop="20250212120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 46 -- Pilgrimage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Christmas Eve in Los Angeles, and Malloy and Reed track down a suspect who beat and mugged a rescue mission Santa, who later gets arrested himself. They also respond to an alcohol-related traffic accident that resulted in a fatality, help a penniless widow who has been detained for shoplifting and take part in the search for a young Native American child who wandered off into a mountainous area while her parents were asleep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212120000 +0000" stop="20250212130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Fairy Godmother Of Dating To The Rescue</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dating expert, Bela Gandhi, helps Toony with his love life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212130000 +0000" stop="20250212133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward must make a decision when a conflict develops concerning which son to spend the weekend with. He can either go on a fishing trip with Wally or take Beaver on a father-son weekend. Thinking Ward is going to go fishing with Wally, Beaver makes up a wild story when his classmates start to tease him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212133000 +0000" stop="20250212140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Chuey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver makes a new friend in Chuey Varella but the boy only speaks Spanish. So Beaver asks Eddie, who has taken Spanish, for some help but Eddie plays a joke on Beaver by feeding him a sentence in Spanish which ultimately insults Chuey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212140000 +0000" stop="20250212150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ancient Romeo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della go out for a night at the theatre to see 'Romeo and Juliet.' After the theatre suddenly goes dark during a dueling scene, the audience is horrified to discover that one of the actors has been killed with a sword when the lights are restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212150000 +0000" stop="20250212160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Evening News: Part 2  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Office pranks get out of hand—and may have led to murder. Matlock takes the case of Billy Finley, a recently fired office employee charged in the murder of another pink-slip recipient.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212160000 +0000" stop="20250212170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Look Back: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Tibbs, Gillespie and Bubba pursue different leads in a bizarre murder case and the Chief realizes that the killer has plans for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212170000 +0000" stop="20250212180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Mary Ellen's mountain patient dies, leaving his young teen to the helping hand</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212180000 +0000" stop="20250212190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Thirty A Month And Found</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Three cattle drivers find that railroads are forcing them out of business. Two of them turn to crime for a temporary fix.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212190000 +0000" stop="20250212200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Dilemma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben helps a convict win a parole only to have the man later become the chief suspect in a bank robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212200000 +0000" stop="20250212203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Quiet Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas' old Army pal settles in North Fork with his deaf daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212203000 +0000" stop="20250212210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sporting Chance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An Englishman arrives with a custom-made rifle—and a plan to kill Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212210000 +0000" stop="20250212220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Annie Duggan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>"An elderly couple and then a young girl become ill with typhoid fever on the wagon train. A young servant girl has attended to them all in isolation. One of the women on the train has an idea about the cause but no one wants to listen."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212220000 +0000" stop="20250212230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl On The Balance Beam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl is in a rush to go to the Olympics. The firemen rescue an actress trapped on a high wire at a studio, extricate a drunk driver from his car and attend to a burning train carrying ammonium nitrate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212230000 +0000" stop="20250212233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Picture This</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter's attempts to assemble the crew for a family portrait are thwarted by a feud between bunkmates Pierce, Hunnicutt and Winchester. Things are not helped by the efforts of Margaret, Klinger and Mulcahy to bring the Swampmen back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250212233000 +0000" stop="20250213000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That Darn Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger buys a goat, with the intention of getting rich by selling its milk. Then the goat eats the 4077th's $22,340 payroll, leaving paymaster Hawkeye holding the bag. Meanwhile, Charles also thinks he can make a killing when he sees an ancient vase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213000000 +0000" stop="20250213003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Look Me Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret and her nursing staff are about to be inspected by Col. Bucholz. Meanwhile, Kellye is offended that Hawkeye is attracted to nurses besides her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213003000 +0000" stop="20250213010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Trick Or Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Halloween at the 4077th, and the staff dons costumes and trades ghost stories. Father Mulcahy discovers a soldier alive that had been pronounced dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213010000 +0000" stop="20250213013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Rich Girlfriend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy has begun seeing Peggy McMillan and he discovers she is from a wealthy family. The differences in their upbringings and education unsettle Andy, and he begins to doubt the ability of the relationship to endure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213013000 +0000" stop="20250213020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The New Mayor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and the new mayor are not on the same page in terms of Andy's style of managing Mayberry's sheriff's department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213020000 +0000" stop="20250213023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Becomes A Banker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is made a bank vice president so he can compete in an interbank skeet shoot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213023000 +0000" stop="20250213030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Blind Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter sets Gomer up with a blind date who thinks he is an oil millionaire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213030000 +0000" stop="20250213033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The General Swap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan captures a German general to trade for an American general who dislikes Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213033000 +0000" stop="20250213040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Brinksmeyer Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan robs a bank to help pay for a map to German rocket installations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213040000 +0000" stop="20250213043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Cher</sub-title>
    <desc>In Dual Pianos, a great pianist tries to calm his protege before they play together. Then in TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parody TV products, including Wish Detergent, Long Distance Phone Call, L'eggs Pantyhose, Buff-Up Toothpaste, and Second Cup of Coffee. Finally, in The Not So Eternal Triangle, a beautiful woman finds she can't compete with her frumpy husband's mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213043000 +0000" stop="20250213053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Stuttering Bishop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Bishop Arthur Mallory is met in his hotel room by Wallace Lang, an associate of a wealthy man named Charles Burroughs. He is warned through physical violence to stop looking for Burroughs' granddaughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213053500 +0000" stop="20250213060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Night Of A Jockey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A dejected jockey wants to be tall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213060500 +0000" stop="20250213063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Me Twice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman commits murder while under hypnosis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213063500 +0000" stop="20250213070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Tea Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman confronts the wife of a rich man and tries to convince her to give her husband a divorce.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213070500 +0000" stop="20250213080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Death Has No Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix's search for the source of a death threat takes him to a small town. Shortly after he arrives, he's framed for murder and imprisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213080500 +0000" stop="20250213090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Lady's Tears</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a plane carrying three million in negotiable securities vanishes, the insurance carrier hires Cannon to find out what happened to it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213090500 +0000" stop="20250213100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Perchance To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An affair leads to an accidental murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213100000 +0000" stop="20250213103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly apartment manager is found to have been beaten to death with a hammer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213103000 +0000" stop="20250213110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Candy Store Robberies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to figure out a pattern to a series of candy store hold-ups. The solution comes when they discover that there are two suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213110000 +0000" stop="20250213113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 85 -- Sign Of The Twins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed start the shift with a call to a liquor store robbery, where a fellow officer was shot but the owner of the store appears to be lying. Further investigation pushes the owner to admit one of the thieves was his brother and he was trying to protect him. In the meantime, they have a zoning issue with an elderly astrology reader followed by the report of a young boy asking a pharmacist questions about Seconal pills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213113000 +0000" stop="20250213120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 175 -- Con Artists</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy respond to a car rollover where a good samaritan makes matters worse. Afterward, they respond to several victims of a well-known family of seasonal home improvement con artists before finally catching them in the act. In the meantime, they search for a disgruntled ex-employee who is trying to sabotage his former workplace, and take a drunk driver off the street.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213120000 +0000" stop="20250213130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Love Through The Ages</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony discuss the evolution of dating."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213130000 +0000" stop="20250213133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Watch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While watching Wally and his friends play baseball, Beaver is put in charge of looking after everyone's coats and watches. However, after the game is over Lumpy comes to claim his watch, but Beaver has no watch to give him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213133000 +0000" stop="20250213140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Her Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver becomes good friends with a classmate, Linda Dennison. However, their relationship is blown out of proportion by Beaver's classmates who begin to tease him and goad him into insulting Linda to prove that she isn't his girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213140000 +0000" stop="20250213150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Promoter's Pillbox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Aspiring screenwriter Herbert Simms submits a teleplay to unscrupulous producer Charlie Corby, who passes the manuscript off as his own. Corby's scheme dies with him, however, when he is fatally whacked over the head with a whiskey bottle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213150000 +0000" stop="20250213160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassination: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock and his daughter, Leanne, become mired in a case involving local politics and murder when the town mayor is assassinated and soon after that a judge is implicated in another death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213160000 +0000" stop="20250213170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The murder of well-respected man turns up a shocking secret about his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213170000 +0000" stop="20250213180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Revel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy returns to New York with a new book - that is not good</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213180000 +0000" stop="20250213190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Wiving</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S20E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Farmer Jed Hockett (Harry Morgan) orders his three boys to go to town and return with prospective brides.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213190000 +0000" stop="20250213200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Brass Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Juan Ortega claims he has a land grant which gives him ownership of the entire Nevada Territory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213200000 +0000" stop="20250213203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Salinas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Banker Hamilton is closing up for the day when Rudy Gray persuades him to stay open for one more transaction—a withdrawal at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213203000 +0000" stop="20250213210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Two Ounces Of Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sammy Davis Jr. stars as Tip Corey, son of a man allegedly murdered in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213210000 +0000" stop="20250213220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Michael Mcgoo Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>"When four brothers are orphaned, no one on the train wants all four. Charlie is determined to find a home for the four together and even proposes to a spinster who wants the boys but turns him down so he looks for a husband for her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213220000 +0000" stop="20250213230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Involvement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Rampart's former Emergency! department head nurse tries to commit suicide; she is brought to Rampart, where she befriends a paraplegic child who almost drowned in a swimming pool. Also: a woman wrapped in plastic, a family suffering from carbon monoxide poisoning and a man pinned under a tank truck containing volatile fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213230000 +0000" stop="20250213233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Foreign Affairs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Army tries to get a North Korean pilot to defect, and Charles gets a rude shock when he falls for a French nurse with a Bohemian past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250213233000 +0000" stop="20250214000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Is Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of reminders about Trapper John's skill as a practical joker, B.J. bets Hawkeye he can prank everyone present.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214000000 +0000" stop="20250214003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Who Knew?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye volunteers to deliver the eulogy for a dead nurse that he briefly dated, and belatedly discovers her deep feelings for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214003000 +0000" stop="20250214010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombshells</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing the theory that people will believe in anything, Charles and Hawkeye start a rumor that Marilyn Monroe plans to visit the 4077th, which gets everyone excited. Meanwhile, B.J. feels responsible when he's unable to rescue a wounded soldier, and is less than impressed when he is presented with a Bronze Star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214010000 +0000" stop="20250214013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Bachelors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie are left alone while Aunt Bee goes out of town. Peggy, Andy's new girlfriend, takes great delight in helping the boys handle things. Floyd warns Andy that Peggy is using her feminine wiles to "snare" him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214013000 +0000" stop="20250214020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Cow Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The mayor calls in an investigator from the state capital to help solve a string of cow thefts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214020000 +0000" stop="20250214023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An authority on American history finds evidence that Jed's ancestors preceded the Mayflower to America.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214023000 +0000" stop="20250214030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Home On The Range</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer helps out a family by finding them shelter in a shack, unaware that the shack is the target of impending war games.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214030000 +0000" stop="20250214033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Praise The Fuhrer And Pass The Ammunition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men create chaos during staged war games that a ruthless Nazi colonel has scheduled near Stalag 13, replacing the exercise's fake explosives with live ammunition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214033000 +0000" stop="20250214040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan And The Lady Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan resents having a lady scientist in charge of a mission to destroy a lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214040000 +0000" stop="20250214043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Hollow Hero, the Queen and King try to give their Hollow solider a blue pony. Then, in The Family, Eunice finds out her husband went into a massage parlor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214043000 +0000" stop="20250214053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lost Last Act</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Playwright Ernest Royce is found shot to death in the same manner as a character in one of his un-produced plays. The play deals with characters very close to real people and the real-life murder of a New York underworld figure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214053500 +0000" stop="20250214060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Living Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is displeased when his wife buys an expensive doll for his step-daughter. He becomes even more displeased when the doll tells him it doesn't like him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214060500 +0000" stop="20250214063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>And The Desert Shall Blossom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Two old men face being evicted from their shack when they show no evidence of self-support.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214063500 +0000" stop="20250214070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Herman And Mrs. Fenimore</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Two women scheme to get rid of a rich old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214070500 +0000" stop="20250214080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Small Favor For An Old Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix loses a friend, a small time mob courier killed flying money to Mexico. The mobsters, certain Mannix stole their loot, come after the detective with a vengeance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214080500 +0000" stop="20250214090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Limping Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer confined to a psychiatric hospital escapes. He's looking for his wife, whom he believes framed him for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214090500 +0000" stop="20250214100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Loose Connection, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is used to smuggle narcotics.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250214100000 +0000" stop="20250214103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Fur Job</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gannon goes undercover as a buyer in order to trap fur thieves"</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
